Si Xingxuan.
I was wrong about you.
What is wrong with me?
How could I get angry at Cangyue?
Cangyue.
Brother.
Brother, you haven't walked the dog
with me for days.
Can you
play with me today?
Are you unhappy, Brother?
Brother, you have wrinkles here.
I made
Sister Cangyue angry.
Can you help me
call Sister Cangyue over?
Okay?
Why should I go?
Girls need to be coaxed.
Brother, you are a fool.
Even Pixiu is smarter than you.
First sweep, sweep away the psychos.
Second sweep, sweep away the jinx.
Third sweep, sweep away Si Xingxuan.
Fourth sweep...
Boss, why did you give up the comfortable job
of serving tea and pouring water,
and insist on sweeping the floor outside?
You're going to sweep a hole in the ground.
Because I was born to sweep floors.
His Majesty hasn't come out for two days.
I wonder what's wrong.
Lady Cangyue has been acting weird lately too.
She hasn't gone in to serve tea to His Majesty for days.
Could His Majesty be heartbroken?
Boss, what's wrong?
Yeah, tell us.
We'll help you figure it out.
Forget it.
You guys should leave.
Go!
I'm so angry my makeup is ruined.
Cangyue.
Get lost!
I won't.
You won't leave, right?
If you don't leave, I'll dump you.
I won't leave even if you try to get rid of me.
You didn't.
Don't move. Go back.
I'm leaving.
I'm really leaving.
What are you doing?
Alright.
So annoying.
Just say what you want to say.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
What? I have to leave just because you tell me to?
Do I have to forgive you just because you say sorry?